《24小时：再活一天》 第九季 第十二集
《24小时：再活一天》前情提要
我们付你钱  研发这个超驰装置
We paid you to develop the override,
为的可不是让你贡献给全世界
not for you to give it away to the rest of the world.
你和成合作
You're working with Cheng?
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
克洛伊·奥布莱恩
成绑架了杰克  把他扔进了某处城外的
Cheng kidnapped Jack, had him put in a secret prison
秘密监狱  折磨了一年多
outside of Beijing and tortured him for over a year.
奥德莉去找杰克时
When Audrey went to go look for him,
他对她故技重施
he did the same thing to her.
你对我已经没什么用了
I really don't have any use for you anymore.
发送吧
Send it.
指令已发送
并且身处英格兰
and he's here in England.
航母的沉没
Our carrier sinking
以及舰上数千名船员的死
and the deaths of thousands of crewmen
是一种无耻的战争行为  不能坐视不理
is a brazen act of war that cannot go unanswered.
你一定要找到成
It's imperative that you find Cheng
以及超驰装置  以便我们对某国做出解释
and the override device, so that we can show the XX
这事不是我们所为
that we were not responsible.
可鲍尔依然知道我们的底细
Bauer is still in the picture.
你早该把他干掉的
You were supposed to have taken him out.
我派了一队人去抓他回来
I sent a team to recover him.
他不找到我是不会罢休的
He's not gonna stop until he finds me.
成志
我的人会在码头等你
My people will meet you at the dock.
只需不到一小时你就能离开这个国家
You'll be out of the country in less than an hour.
把目击者带上
Bring the witness.
她脑袋里的东西可是价值连城
What's in her head is extremely valuable.
你设计让俄国人抓我  狗娘养的  为什么
You set me up for the Russians, you son of a bitch. Why?!
白宫参谋长
马克·布德罗
当时我还以为鲍尔叛国
I thought Bauer was a traitor.
我还以为他来这是为了暗杀您
I thought he was here to assassinate you.
四年来  俄国人一直催促我们
The Russians have been pushing us for four years
把他交给他们
to turn him over to them.
我在引渡令上伪造了您的签名
I forged your signature on the rendition order.
我正式以叛国罪逮捕你
I am placing you under arrest for treason.
总统阁下  他对我还有用处
Mr. President, I can still use him.
我需要他安排一次会面
I'm gonna need him to set up a meet.
他在大出血  帮我拿条毛巾  快
He's bleeding out. Get me a towel now!
成在哪
Where is Cheng?!
我的国家没有忘记
My country has not forgotten.
他们不会放弃
They will not give up until you pay
直到你为自己的行为付出代价
for what you have done.
我有一个在某国驻伦敦使馆的联络人
I have a contact at the XX Embassy here in London.
奥德莉·布德罗
让我安排一次会面
Let me arrange a meeting
我会把能证明我们的系统
and I will bring evidence
遭到入侵而不受我们控制的证据
that the penetration of our systems
带给她
was out of our control.
请尽快把这个交给令尊
Please take this to your father as quickly as possible.
娇  谢谢你
Jiao... thank you.
我部下的枪口正对准了你
My associate has his weapon trained on you.
坐回到长椅上  不许动
Sit back down on the bench and don't move.
也许我还能留你一条活路
Maybe I'll allow you to live.
以下事件发生于晚上10:00到上午11:00间
娇
Jiao?
天哪
My God.
我警告过你  坐在凳子上别动
I told you, you may not move from the bench.
可是我的朋友还活着
But my friend is still alive.
我想去看看能否救她
Let me go see if I can help her.
我不会跑的
I won't run.
我保证
I give you my word.
我现在去看看能否救她
I'm going to her to see if I can help her.
别叫
Do not scream.
别和任何人联系
Do not communicate with anyone in any way.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你到底想怎样
What do you want?
你再离开凳子一次
You move from the bench again,
我的狙击手就会杀了你
my sniper will kill you.
坐下
Sit.
斯托纳维奇的电邮似乎都是私人信件
Stolnavich's e-mails all look like they're personal.
都是发给家人和不同的女人的
To family, different women.
会是用某种方式加密了的吗
Could it be in some sort of code?
就算是加密过的  斯托纳维奇也不会
Stolnavich wouldn't have kept something like that in the open,
留着这些信件的
even if it was coded.
找到一封在三天前用假名发来的电邮
I got e-mails from three days ago using a false name
以及船运付款的安排
and arranging for payments for a shipment.
今晚离境
Leaves tonight.
成肯定会上那艘船
Cheng's got to be that shipment.
他会在四十分钟内乘着货船离开海港
He's gonna be on a freighter from the harbor in less than 40 minutes.
好  我呼叫支援
Okay, I'll call it in.
我让艾瑞克马上派一支小队过去
I'll get Erik to send a team there right now.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What is it?
我是摩根特工
This is Agent Morgan.
我需要派一支小队去南汉普顿
I'm gonna need a team sent down to South Hampton.
时间标识  这是一分钟前拍的
This time stamp-- this was taken less than a minute ago.
挂掉电话
Hang up the phone.
-立刻挂掉电话  -我一会再打回来
- Hang up the phone now. - I'll call back.
说吧
Yes?
别再追踪我
Stop tracking me.
我一旦安全离境  即刻放人
As soon as I'm safely away, I will set her free.
如果你来抓我  或找人解救她
If you come near me or anyone try to help her,
-她将即刻毙命  -成  听我说
- she dies instantly. - Cheng, please listen to me...
这就是我的条件
Those are my terms!
听清楚了吗
Is that clear?
清楚了
Yes.
成
Cheng?
Cheng?!
结束了  结束了
So... it's over. It's over.
我们  我们不能去抓他
We-we... we can't go after him.
抓住成是唯一能避免
Getting to Cheng is the only way
与某国发生战争的办法
we're gonna stop this war with XX.
这只是你的假设
You're just assuming that.
我们也不知道这样是否能向卫主席证明
We don't know if we can get the proof to President Wei!
或者他看到证据后  是否会撤回命令
Or even if he'll back off when he gets it.
我们这是毫无意义地害死奥德莉
We're condemning Audrey to death for nothing.
我们别无选择
We don't have another choice.
她爱你
She loves you.
闭嘴
Shut up!
摩根特工
Agent Morgan.
我们不能让中情局参与此事
We can't involve the CIA.
他们很容易被成发现
Cheng will see them coming from a mile away.
还有什么别的办法
What's the alternative?
他说得对  我们别无选择
He's right, there isn't one.
我要去救奥德莉
I need to go after Audrey.
杰克  总统直接下令
Jack, you're under a direct order from the President
要你去抓成  你必须服从指令
to go after Cheng; you got to follow that.
我去救奥德莉
I can go after Audrey.
你真的觉得你能处理此事吗
You really think you can handle this?
能
Yes.
好  我要你谨慎地联系奥德莉的办公室
Okay, I want you to contact Audrey's office discreetly.
查出她的去向
Find out where she was going.
不管你怎么做  千万不要让中情局知道
Whatever you do, do not alert the CIA.
我要你召集一个小队
I want you to put together a small team.
除掉狙击手
You take out that sniper.
每一步行动都要通知我
You keep me posted every step of the way.
我会的
I will.
总统阁下
Mr. President,
我是艾瑞克·雷特特工  情报站代理站长
I'm Agent Erik Ritter, acting head of station.
您的军事顾问正在楼上的
Your military advisors are set up in our secure comm
紧急通讯及情报中心待命
and briefing facilities upstairs.
谢谢你  雷特特工
Well, thank you, Agent Ritter.
奥德莉那边有消息吗
Have you heard anything from Audrey?
我十五分钟前
I checked in on their Secret Service detail
跟特勤组联系过
15 minutes ago.
她还在跟辛娇谈话
She and Jiao Sim were still talking.
鲍尔呢
What about Bauer?
鲍尔还没有消息  阁下
Negative on Bauer, sir.
现在情况如何  上将
What's our status, Admiral?
中方派出了八个两栖登陆小队
The Chinese now have eight amphibious landing groups
正接近我们在冲绳的基地
steaming toward our bases in Okinawa.
第一艘中方航母将在半小时内
The first Chinese carrier to reach the 12-mile limit
进入十二英里界限
will be in the next half hour.
第七舰队已接到命令
At which point, the seventh fleet
准备迎战
has standing orders to engage.
同时  中方核潜艇
Also, they've ordered their nuclear armed submarines
已升至水下三百英尺
to ascend to 300 feet--
发射深度
firing depth.
阁下  我们需要您的授权
Sir, we need your authorization
以提升我方核反击的战备等级
to escalate our own nuclear readiness in response.
让潜艇及发射井进入最高战备状态
Put our subs and silos on the highest alert.
看能否帮我接通卫主席
See if you can get President Wei on the line.
亲爱的  你没事吧
Love, are you okay?
你没事吧  亲爱的
Are you all right, love?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
我能用一下你的手机吗
Can I use your phone, please?
当然可以
Yes. Yes, of course.
是谁
Who is this?
杰克  是我
Jack, it's me.
克洛伊  你在哪里
Chloe, where are you?
我落在成手里  我跳了车
Cheng had me; I jumped out of his truck.
阿德里安死了
Adrian's dead.
我知道
I know.
你收到我的信息了
You got my message.
你知道他利用装置
You know he used the device
发动了对某国航母的袭击
to launch the attack on the XX carrier?
对  如果我能活捉成
Yes, and if I capture Cheng alive
并且证明他参与了今天的袭击
and can prove his involvement in today's attack,
我们也许可以避免与某国的战争
we might be able to get XX to back down from war.
你知道他在哪吗
Do you know where he is?
他要坐货轮离开
He's leaving on a cargo ship.
贝尔切克到时在码头跟我会合
Belcheck's meeting me down at the docks.
你不能就这么贸然过去
You can't go in there blind.
我在米尔斯伍德  离码头不远  来接我
I'm at Millswood, not far from the docks. Come get me.
我为你们提供协助
I'll run comm for you.
我能拿到卫星图和地形图
I'll get you satellites, schematics.
克洛伊  这样不太好
Chloe, I don't think that's a good idea.
杰克  我知道你不相信我
Jack, I know you don't trust me.
阿德里安骗了我
Adrian lied to me.
我唯一做错的就是相信了他
The only thing I did wrong was to believe him.
拜托了  让我修正自己的错误
Please, let me make this right.
告诉我位置  我去接你
Give me your cross streets; I'll pick you up.
已接通卫主席  随时可以开始通话
President Wei, whenever you're ready.
接通吧
Go.
主席阁下
Mr. President.
恕我直言
Forgive me for being blunt.
您已向冲绳方向派出海军
You've got your navy heading toward Okinawa,
我方第七舰队已做好防御准备
which our Seventh Fleet is ready to defend.
但我们双方都希望能避免战争
But it's in both our interests to avoid a shooting war.
尤其是两国核武器
Especially with both our countries
都已进入高度战备状态
at a high-level of nuclear readiness.
击沉我方航母
The destruction of our carrier
杀害我方将士的行为是一种挑衅
and the deaths of our soldiers is a provocation.
我们的军队必须做出回应
Our military must respond.
我们已经派出了特工
We have agents in the field in the process of
正在追捕成志
apprehending Cheng Zhi.
与此同时
While that's happening,
我请求您  做出善意之举
I'm asking you, as a gesture of good faith,
让贵国海军停止前进
to halt your naval advance.
我方的官方界定是
Our military's official position
成已经死了
is that Cheng is dead.
我和其他政治局的同志们必须
Myself and my allies in the Politburo
接受这一点  除非有任何证据显示他还活着
must accept this is true, unless proven otherwise.
您说得很清楚了  主席阁下
You've made yourself clear, Mr. President.
我也把话说清楚
Let me make myself clear.
一旦贵国部队越过冲绳以外
Once your forces cross the 12-mile limit
十二英里的界限
outside of Okinawa...
我方就会开火
we will fight.
让你的人上船  不要被人发现
Get your men on board and out of sight.
预计十五分钟后出发
We are scheduled to depart in 15 minutes.
能不能快一点
Is there a way to expedite this?
那会引来我们都不想看到的麻烦
That would draw scrutiny neither of us want.
上船  开始防卫阵地
克洛伊  进来
Chloe, get in.
怎么回事
What the hell happened?
你还好吗
You okay?
我还好
Yeah, I'm fine.
都是逃离成的时候磕碰的
I got banged up getting away from Cheng.
我们时间不多了
We don't have a lot of time.
路上我会解释的
I'll explain everything while we drive.
通讯设备呢
Where is your communications setup?
后座的箱子里
The trunk in the backseat.
克洛伊  我必须知道你拿到超驰装置的时候
Chloe, I need to know why you were with Adrian Cross
为什么会和阿德里安·克洛斯在一起
when you took the override device.
杰克  我试图从阿德里安手上拿走装置
Jack, I tried to get the device from Adrian,
但是他有枪
but he had a gun.
我们回到基地的时候  成已经等在那里了
We got back to the base and Cheng was waiting.
阿德里安和我想得不一样
Adrian wasn't who I thought he was.
他利用了我
He manipulated me
并且利用了我来开发装置
and he used my knowledge to create the device.
所以这有一部分是我的错
So, this is partly my fault.
所以我才要帮你
That's why I need to help you.
我想要弥补过错
I need to try to make this right.
你决定吧
It's up to you.
这个时候
At this point,
恐怕我是你唯一的朋友了
I think I'm the only friend you have left.
不管你愿不愿意承认
Whether you want to admit it or not.
行动很简单
The operation's simple.
活捉成
Capture Cheng alive.
为什么你会一个人  怎么不叫中情局帮忙
Why are you doing this alone? Why not ask the CIA for help?
因为他的狙击手锁定了奥德莉
Because he's got Audrey pinned down by a sniper.
如果发现任何针对他的行动  就会杀了她
He'll kill her if he sees any operation moving against him.
杰克  我很抱歉
Jack, I'm sorry.
这不是你的错  克洛伊
It's not your fault, Chloe.
别想那么多了
You need to let that go.
都不是你的错
None of this is.
奥德莉  我是凯特·摩根
Audrey, this is Kate Morgan.
我是杰克·鲍尔的同事  我是来帮你的
I'm working with Jack Bauer. I'm here to help you.
不管我说什么都不要有任何反应  这很重要
It's really important that you don't react to what I'm saying
因为我们不想让狙击手知道
because we don't want the sniper to know
你在和我通话  明白了吗
that you're in communication with me. Okay?
如果明白就点个头
Nod if you understand what I'm saying.
好的  我需要知道你知不知道狙击手在哪里
Okay, I need to know if you have any idea where the sniper is.
如果不知道就往下看
Look down if the answer is no.
听着  我知道成不想杀了你
Listen, I know Cheng doesn't want to kill you.
我需要你相信我
You're gonna have to trust me on this.
我需要你诱使狙击手开火
I'm gonna need you to draw the sniper's fire
这样我才能知道他的准确位置
so that I can locate exactly where he is.
如果愿意的话就点下头
Nod if you're still with me on this.
好的  我会数到三
Okay, I'm gonna count to three,
到三的时候  我需要你突然移动一下
and on three, I need you to make a sudden movement.
好吗  准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
一
One...
二
Two...
三
Three.
我发现他了  你留在原地
I've got him. Just stay put
我就在这帮你  明白吗
and just know that I'm here, okay?
她开始逃跑  我开枪把她吓回去了
如果情况变化  就杀了她
杰克
Jack.
-现在情况如何  -我找到了狙击手的位置
- What's your status? - I've located the sniper,
但我需要进入指定位置
But I need to move into position
才能用火力掩护奥德莉逃跑
So I can lay down some cover fire for Audrey to run.
收到  安全救出她之后马上告诉我
Copy that. Get back to me as soon as you've got her secured.
明白
Got it.
我们四个一起行动的话
Four of us moving in
就会太引人注意
is just gonna attract too much attention.
我先去踩点
I'm gonna run point.
等我能看清了
The minute I have a clean line of sight,
就听我的命令行动
we move on my command.
-东西拿齐了吗  -齐了
- Did you get everything?  - Yes.
在这里有很多地方供成的手下藏身
There are too many places for Cheng's men to hide.
所以我才要来
That's what I'm here for.
我应该可以黑进一个卫星
I should be able to backdoor a satellite
定位他们的位置
and get their positions.
调制解调器没有信号  我得上线才行
Cellular modem's not giving me a signal. I need to get online.
我可以连接到那个天线上
I can wire into that dish.
我得重编脉冲转发器的程序
I need to reprogram the transponders.
我开着耳麦  稍后联系你
My comm is open. I'll get back to you.
掩护我
Cover me.
克洛伊  等等
Chloe. Wait.
谢谢你
Thank you...
所做的一切
for everything.
祝你好运  快走
And good luck. Go.
奥德莉
Audrey,
我快要进入可以射杀狙击手的指定位置了
I'm about to move into position where I can get a clean shot on the sniper.
等我到达位置后
As soon as that happens,
你一听到枪声
the second you hear a gun fire
就跑进你左后方的树丛
I want you to run toward the tree behind your left shoulder.
好的  别挂电话
Okay, stand by.
杰克  我黑进了我们上方的一颗卫星
Jack, I'm backdoored into a satellite overhead.
正在解析红外热成像
Resolving the infrared.
好了  我可以看到你和贝尔切克
Okay, I can see you and Belcheck.
你们安全了  行动
You're clear. Go.
停下  杰克  有两个守卫
Stop, Jack. You have two guards
正朝你们走来
coming straight at you.
准备好了吗  就现在
Ready? Now.
杰克  还有一个人在集装箱顶上
Jack, there's another guy on top of the container.
-五点钟方向  -收到
- Five o'clock. - Got it.
这里转弯  行动
Turn here. Go.
杰克  你还要解决
Jack, you'll have to take out
两个在左舷的守卫
two guards on the port side.
有人在舰桥上
There are men on the bridge.
他们正在离开
They're moving away.
你们安全了  行动
You're good. Clear. Go.
收到
Copy that.
我们同步射击
Synchronized shot.
我已瞄准左边敌人  你瞄准右边的
I've acquired target on the left; you take target on the right.
我数到三  三  二  一  开枪
On my count. Three, two, one, fire.
克洛伊  我们上船了
Chloe, we're on the boat.
杰克  有敌人在你左侧楼梯上方
Jack, you have a man at the top of the stairs to your left;
还有一个在你正前方的集装箱上
there's another one on the container directly in front of you.
我还检测到了大约十二个在船上的热源信号
I'm picking up about a dozen other heat signatures on the ship,
大多都是两人一组
mostly in pairs.
收到
Copy that.
奥德莉怎么样了
What's the status on Audrey?
我没听到什么消息
I haven't heard anything.
大多数人都在通讯塔周围防守
Most of the men are in a defensive formation around the comm tower--
成肯定在那里
that must be where Cheng is.
-领我们进去  -好的
- Guide us in. - Okay.
头儿  我正在扫描  有人在附近
Sir. I've been running scans-- someone in the immediate area
正用本地卫星进行下行传输
is downstreaming with a local satellite.
清点你的手下
Roll-call your men.
马拉  报到
帕维尔  听得见吗
不管谁在使用卫星
Whoever's linking to the satellite,
你能切断访问和通讯吗
can you cut the access and the communication?
能  我能把他们的信号转发到我的屏幕上
Yes, and I can redirect their feed to my screen.
快点
Do it.
联系留下的人  让他们找到他  快去
Contact whoever's left. Tell them to go find him. Go!
你们跟上去
快点
-他们在干什么  -不
- What are they doing? - No.
天哪
Oh, my God.
成知道我们在这里
Cheng knows we're here.
杰克  我得告诉凯特  她需要马上离开
Jack, I have to tell Kate. She needs to move now.
收到
Copy that.
凯特  我是克洛伊
Kate, it's Chloe.
他们盯上我们了  你得带着奥德莉离开
They're onto us. You have to get Audrey out of there
-让中情局增援  -我正要行动  克洛伊
- and get the CIA involved. - I'm about to move into position, Chloe.
成要下令狙击手开枪了
Cheng's gonna order the sniper to shoot!
把奥德莉带走  快
Get Audrey out of there now. Move.
杀了她
开火  开火
Engage! engage!
快走  快走
Go! go! go!
好了  干掉他了  上去看看确保他死了
Okay, got him. Get up there and make sure he's dead.
奥德莉  你没事吧
Audrey, are you okay?
没事
Yes.
艾瑞克  我是凯特
Erik, it's Kate.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我和奥德莉·布德罗在摩尔登公园
I'm at Malden Park with Audrey Boudreau.
通知特勤局我们保证了她的安全
Inform secret service that we have secured her
正要把她带回中情局
and we're taking her back to the CIA.
-她现任的安保人员呢  -我稍后会一一说明
- Where's her current detail? - I'll explain everything later.
现在你们需要派队前往南汉普顿码头
Right now you need to get a team over to South Hampton Docks.
杰克准备潜入  可他遇到麻烦了
Jack was going in stealth but right now he's in trouble
他现在需要你们的帮助
and he really needs your help--
-他正试图阻止这场战争  -凯特
- he's trying to stop this war. - Kate...
我需要战术小队齐装上直升机  马上
I need tac teams suited up in choppers, now!
杰克  奥德莉安全了
Jack, Audrey's safe.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
他们拦截了我的卫星信号  我连不上卫星了
They've jacked my feed. I've lost satellite,
我正在想办法重连
and I'm trying to get it back...
克洛伊  克洛伊
Chloe? Chloe?
杰克  杰克  杰克  听得到吗
Jack? Jack! Jack, do you copy?
信号丢失
我切断了通讯  接管了他们的卫星信号
I've cut communications and taken over their satellite feed.
这两个信号
These two... signatures...
一定是鲍尔
Must be Bauer
和他的同伙
and whoever he has with him.
我们马上离开
We're leaving now.
跟我走
启动引擎
他们准备开船了
They're getting ready to push off.
我需要你下到引擎室
I need you to get down to the engine room,
尽一切办法阻止开船
do whatever you can to stop,
我会到舰桥上去  快去
and I'll make my way to the bridge. Go.
杰克找到成了吗
Is Jack closing in on Cheng?
是的  成想利用你抓住杰克
Yes. Cheng was using you to get to Jack.
所以杰克把我派过来
That's why Jack sent me here.
杰克没事吧
Is Jack all right?
不知道
I don't know.
趴下
Get down!
两人中枪
Got two men down.
天哪  奥德莉
Oh, God. Audrey.
不
No.
联系艾瑞克  告诉他另有人袭击
Call Erik, tell him we have a second shooter.
那个给我
Give me that.
快叫医务人员来
Get medical here right now!
天哪
Oh, my God.
挺住
Stay with us.
艾瑞克  马上叫医疗队过来
Erik, we need medical now!
奥德莉·布德罗中枪了
Audrey Boudreau's been hit.
挺住
Stay with me.
成安排了两个枪手
Cheng had a second shooter.
坚持住  奥德莉  拜托
With me, Audrey. Come on.
坚持住
Stay with me.
天哪
Oh, God.
好了  坚持住  坚持住
Okay. Stay with me. Stay with me.
坚持住
Stay with me.
奥德莉  挺住
Audrey, will you stay with...?
拜托  奥德莉
Please, Audrey.
你不能... 奥德莉
You're not gonna... Audrey,
求你坚持住  好吗  坚持住
Please stay with me. Stay with me, okay? Stay with me!
天哪
Oh, God.
上将
Admiral?
空中侦察确认
Air reconnaissance confirms.
中方的两栖战队还在向
The Chinese amphibious groups are still on course
我们在冲绳的基地推进
for our base in Okinawa.
总统阁下
Mr. President,
如果他们越界了  我需要您批准交战
I need a go-ahead to engage if the perimeter is breached.
杰克有消息吗
Anything from Jack?
目前没有  总统阁下
I'm afraid not, Mr. President.
阁下  我们的部队在等您的命令
Sir, our forces are awaiting your orders.
我知道  上校
I know that, colonel.
长官  我有话跟您说
Sir... I need a word.
私下说
Private.
贝尔切克
Belcheck?
我得给枪上膛
I got to fall back to reset.
收到
Copy that.
克洛伊
Chloe.
杰克  我是凯特
Jack, it's Kate.
说吧
Yeah, go ahead.
杰克  我很抱歉
Jack, I'm so sorry.
奥德莉死了
We lost Audrey.
你在说什么  你说她安全了的
What are you talking about? You said she was safe.
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
还有一个枪手  射中了她  杰克
There was another shooter, and he got her, Jack.
我...我很抱歉
I'm-I'm so sorry.
杰克
Jack?
杰克  听到我说话吗
Jack, can you hear me?
杰克  说话
Jack, talk to me.
关掉发动机
Engine-- turn it off.
你本该躲躲藏藏
You should have stayed hidden like a rat.
本还可以终老一生
You could have died an old man.
警告
十二英里  越界
中方越界了  总统阁下
The Chinese have breached the perimeter, Mr. President.
批准交战
Permission to engage.
武器设定为"红色战备"状态[确认敌意下方可开火]
Set weapon postures red and tight.
批准对任何确认的
You are cleared to engage any positively-identified
中方的空中或水面目标开火
Chinese air or surface targets.
总统阁下  如果形势升级
Mr. President, if this should escalate,
我们需要复核一下核反击方案
We need to begin reviewing the nuclear response scenario.
开始复核吧
Begin the review.
阁下  我把楼下的紧急电话接过来
Sir, I'm putting through an urgent call from downstairs.
打扰一下  各位
Excuse me, gentlemen.
我跟杰克·鲍尔连线上了
I have Jack Bauer on live comm link.
暂停命令
Hold that order.
先暂缓武器"红色战备"状态
Delay weapon posture red.
转到显示器上
Putting it up on the monitors.
我是杰克·鲍尔
This is Jack Bauer.
我抓住成志了  他活着
I have Cheng Zhi, and he is alive.
我抓住成了  他活着
I have Cheng, and he is alive.
启动面部识别
Initiate facial recognition.
收到  刚连上中方
Copy that. Just connected with the Chinese.
等我一下
Just give me one second.
你正在被录像
You're being recorded.
告诉他们你是谁
Tell them who you are.
确认好了吗
Do we have confirmation yet?
再有几秒钟就好  阁下
Just a few more seconds, sir.
告诉他们你是谁
Tell them who you are!
我是成志
My name is Cheng Zhi!
收到了吗
Did you get that?
Did you get that?!
收到
Got it.
面部识别和语音识别都匹配
That's facial recognition and voice match.
是他
It's him.
明白
Copy that.
离线
Out.
连线卫主席
Let's get President Wei on the line.
这是为了奥德莉  你个狗娘养的
This is for Audrey, you son of a bitch.
主席阁下
Mr. President,
收到我们刚发给你的文件了吗
did you receive the file we just sent you?
我正在看
I'm looking at it now.
你能看到  成还活着  被我们抓获了
Then you can see that Cheng is alive and in our custody.
这就印证了我对你说的
This confirms everything I've told you
关于沈阳舰沉没的事情
about the sinking of the Shenyang.
不是我下的令
It was not my order.
我们得证实这段视频
We will need to verify this recording.
随你证实  但同时
Well, you can verify it all you want, but in the meantime,
你得让你的战舰撤退
you need to turn your ships around.
你的战舰已经穿越了我们的防线
Your ships have crossed our defensive perimeter.
如果你不撤退
If you don't turn them around,
我将被迫做出反应
I'm going to be forced to respond.
好
All right.
我会让战舰撤退
I will instruct our ships to withdraw,
但我需要你保证  你方会就
but I need your assurance that we will discuss reparations
我方航母和舰上人员的损失做出赔偿
for the loss of our carrier and the soldiers aboard.
我保证
You have that.
谢谢  主席阁下
And thank you, Mr. President.
阁下
Sir, I, uh...
在我们回国前
Before we head back out, I...
我得和您谈谈
need to talk to you.
说吧
Speak.
内容很敏感  阁下
It's rather sensitive, sir.
也许  也许你可以坐好了听我说
Maybe, uh... maybe you want to sit back down.
我不用坐好
I don't need to sit down.
什么事  告诉我
What happened? Tell me.
阁下
Sir, um...
是奥德莉
It's Audrey.
她死了
She's dead.
她在和辛娇见面的时候  被狙击手枪杀了
She was shot by a sniper during her meeting with Jiao Sim.
是成的人
It was one of Cheng's men.
一定弄错了
That's got to be a mistake.
她是去参加保密会面
She was at a covert meeting.
还有一队特勤安保人员保护
She had Secret Service detail with her.
不可能
That's impossible!
那个特勤小组的所有人都死了
Every man on that detail was killed, as well.
非常抱歉  消息没有错
I'm so sorry, it's not a mistake.
现场也已经确认
We got confirmation from the field
您女儿十分钟前死于枪伤
that your daughter died ten minutes ago from a gunshot wound.
阁下
Sir.
快叫医务员
Get a medic in here, will you?
二楼会议室需要医务员
We need a medic at the second floor conference room.
还好吗
You okay?
阁下  还好吗  慢点  慢点  慢点
Sir, you okay? Okay. Go easy, go easy, go easy, go easy.
慢点
Easy.
好了
It's okay.
-克洛伊  -我们控制船之后
- Chloe? - I haven't heard from her.
就没再听到她
Not since we charged the boat.
克洛伊
Chloe?
杰克
Jack.
不
No.
克洛伊
Chloe!
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
你是谁
Who is this?
什么时候
When?
哪里
Where?
明白了
Understood.
我会去的  你安排吧
I'll be there. Just set it up.
十二小时后
艾瑞克
Erik.
这是我的行动小结
It's my after-action report.
听我说
Look...
奥德莉的死
what happened to Audrey,
不是你的错
it wasn't your fault.
外勤工作不是一门精密科学
Field work is not an exact science.
你不可能知道
There's no way you could have known
成还有一个枪手
that Cheng had a second shooter.
是的  我明白
Yeah, I, uh... I realize that.
根据总统之令
Per the President's orders,
这些人将押送你去累肯赫斯
these men are going to escort you to Lakenheath
在那里  会有一架军机把你送回美国
where a military transport will take you back to the States.
总统怎么样了
How is the President?
我们说话这会儿  总统正登上空军一号
The President is boarding Air Force One as we speak.
詹姆斯  我向你致以最深切的慰问
James, you have my deepest sympathy.
我无法想象你的悲痛
I can't even imagine what you're going through.
谢谢你  阿拉斯泰尔
Thank you, Alastair.
你一直是个好朋友
You've been a good friend.
如果我能为你做点什么  任何事
If there's anything I can do, anything at all...
不  你什么都做不了
No, there's nothing you can do.
谁都无能为力
Nothing anyone can do.
我们动身来伦敦的前一天
The day before we left for London,
我坐在我的办公室里
I was sitting in my office
看着我桌上一个美丽女人的照片
looking at a picture on my desk of a beautiful woman.
我一直看着她
I kept staring at it.
从我就职第一天起  照片就摆在桌上
It's been on my desk since my first day in office.
我知道我认识那个女人
And I knew that I knew that woman.
但我却想不起她的名字
But I couldn't think of her name.
十秒  十五秒过去  突然
Ten seconds, 15 seconds go by, then, poof.
我想起来了
Pops into my head.
那是奥德莉
It was Audrey.
请节哀
I'm so sorry.
我不会记得今天发生的事
I won't remember anything that happens today.
我不会记得发生过的任何事
I won't remember anything that happens, period.
我不会记得我曾有个女儿
I won't remember that I had a daughter
她死得那么惨
that died in such a horrible fashion.
伦敦城外
你确定你要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to do this?
是的
Yeah.
她先走过来
She walks first!
杰克  你不必这么做的
Jack, you don't have to do this.
是时候让你回家了
It's time for you to go home.
你之前说的没错
You were right about what you said, earlier.
你是我最好的朋友
About being my best friend.
谢谢你
Thank you.
方便的时候去看看我的家人
Look in on my family when you can.
走吧
Go.
我相信你说的是真话
I've taken you at your word.
但如果你对我说谎
But if you're lying to me--
如果她或者我的家人发生任何不测
if anything happens to her or my family--
那你的世界将分崩离析
your entire world will come apart,
而你不会有机会看到那个场面
and you will never see it coming.
我们只要你  鲍尔先生
We just want you, Mr. Bauer.
我们只想要你
That's all we ever wanted.
我本来想说你会享受莫斯科之旅
I would say you're going to enjoy Moscow...
但你会知道我在骗你
but you'd know I was lying.
上车
Go to the car.
快去
Go.